(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
♫I never know what love is like♫
♫All my life, never once have I experienced it♫
♫No one to take that place in my heart♫
♫But now that I’ve met you, my heart begins to glow♫
♫What feeling is this? Why is my heart fluttering?♫
♫And I just can’t control it.♫
♫What happened to my heart right now?♫
♫I can’t control it when you’re around♫
♫This heart…it stops at you♫
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
[Waves of Deception]
[Previously]
It’s none of the girl’s business. Just keep your mouth shut.
When it comes to using brains,
better let the guys handle that.
[Pheempat]: You want to do something to help the Wachara Group, right?
I’ll try to get close to Miss Apo as soon as I can.
You’ll definitely beat the Watin Group this time.
[Nam]: Pretty faces with no brains are not welcome here.
[Lada]: We all make mistakes, don’t we?
If you fire me,
you might make a big mistake there.
All of you together?
[Preem]: But if you want me to find an excuse to fire her…
[Nam]: No need.
Just keep reporting me as it is.
[Lom]: Has Miss Lada been working here long?
Why would you want to know about her?
I want to ask her out.
This one is off limit.
[Lom]: Hold on.
So many guests today.
I can’t believe we’re entering a low season now.
How are you getting along, Lada?
You’re working two shifts in a row. Are you sure you can manage?
See? That’s why I told you to do the night shift another day.
Boss
Yes, Boss.
Chonlada.
Miss Chonlada!
Good evening! Welcome to Monarch Global International!
Were you on an auto-reply mode or what?
Boss?
You’re a receptionist.
Do you think it’s appropriate to take a nap while you’re on duty?
I was just…
Don’t tell me you had no idea you were napping?
You, take it from here.
Yes, Boss.
And you…
Come with me.
She’ll definitely fire me.
[Lom: Sis, are you hiding Chonlada from me?]
Boss.
Boss, I’m so sorry. I didn’t mean it.
I promise I won’t mess up again.
Please don’t fire me.
Please, Boss.
[Lom: Not picking up. Read but no reply. Do you think you can stop me?]
Go over there and sit.
Yes?
Go sit over there.
Why do you want me to sit there?
Just do as I said.
[Lom: You’re in the office, right?]
But what you said doesn’t make sense.
You might be the boss, but you should also have a good reason to make your staff do as you say.
So, why do you want me to stay here with you?
[Lom: Stay right there!]
[Lom: Don’t go anywhere!]
[Nam: Go back to your room. Just do as you’re told.]
You like her, don’t you?
I already told you.
If you don’t, why are you hiding her from me?
You want to keep her away from me, don’t you?
You’ve been drinking, haven’t you?
Just go back to your room.
And listen, I’ll tell you something.
If you don’t want your life to get complicated
you’d better stay away from her.
Boss.
Isn’t that Chonlada?
Where are you now?
I…I’ve got work to do.
Talk to you later.
Hey! Can’t you see I was on the phone?
I do. It’s you who couldn’t see me.
That’s why I have to stick out my face like this.
I still don’t understand why you want me to stay with you in this meeting room?
If there’s nothing else, please excuse me. I have to go downstairs.
Nuch just told me Miss Wayo is looking for me.
Where are you going?
I told you Nuch said Miss Wayo is looking for me.
Then why do you have to go?
To take care of her room, of course.
I already told Miss Wadee to take care of it.
Stay here.
I told her that too. But Nuch insists that Miss Wayo really wants to see me.
She is a guest at our hotel too.
Not to mention that she’s also your sister.
I don't want to get complaint that I was being negligent.
Please excuse me, Boss.
Sit here.
Sit and stay as quiet as you can.
I’ll be right back. I have a job for you.
- But, Boss!
- Quiet!
If you disobey me again,
I’ll fire you this time.
And you can go on and threaten me
or file a charge against me for an unfair dismissal.
I don’t give a damn at all!
So mean!
Possessive of your sister, aren’t you? Good!
You’d better keep me close for a long long time, Boss.
Hey.
She’s so weird. How can she sleep anywhere like this?
3am?
If you’re up, just leave. No need to wake me.
And tell the maid to do the ozone,
cleaning for the couch to prevent the mold from growing on it. You’re drooling in your sleep.
I’m not that dirty.
Are you saying I’m dirty?
Just you wait.
Someone is in there?
This is going to be juicy.
[Maid group]: Got a big fat juicy gossip.
Lada.
Nuch.
You’re here so early.
I’ve been waiting for you.
Why?
What happened?
Don’t tell me…
that Boss wants me to do something for her again.
That’s right, it’s about our boss.
But it’s not about work.
Then what is it about?
So, did you sleep with her?
I’m sorry. Is that what people are talking about?
Doesn’t anyone think that Boss and I were only discussing about work in that room?
You and Boss came out of that room after three in the morning.
I’ve tried my best to believe it was only about work.
But all these years that I’ve been working for the Watin Group,
I’ve never seen Boss summon anyone to discuss about work so late at night apart from Miss Preem and you.
Not even one?
No.
And unlike you, none of the staff who dares to talk back to her has ever managed to keep their job here after that.
She also talks to you more often than she’s ever talked to any of us here.
Well, that’s…
Nuch, please listen.
Actually…
- Right now, every staff here…
thinks that you and Boss already slept together.
So, don’t bother trying to explain anything.
Nobody would listen to you.
Read my lips…”Impossible”.
But I wasn’t trying to deny it.
What do you mean?
So, you and Boss really…
did it?
Geez, Nuch.
I’m a lady somehow.
Don’t make me say it out loud.
Let’s just say, I’ll leave it to Boss to clarify it herself.
So…
How many times?
Actually, I’m not that hungry.
I’d better get back to work.
- Let’go then.
- Okay.
[Nam]: Miss Preem, is there a problem among our staff lately?
Since I’ve walked in, I could feel them looking my way and whispering to each other.
As if they were gossiping about me.
[Preem]: That’s probably because of the rumour lately.
But I honestly have no idea who started it.
[Nam]: What rumour?
Watch out, Boss!
Boss.
Are you okay, Boss?
I’m okay.
[Lom’s calling]
Is she calling about the rumour?
I thought you said Lom already checked out.
Why do you think she’d know about the rumour?
She’s a cop somehow.
And she knows most of the staff here.
It’s possible that she’d hear about it.
Do you want me to stop this rumour?
Never mind.
You know I don’t like to waste my time on something nonsense like this.
And since it’s just a rumour, we’d better let it go.
They’ll forget it soon.
But people don’t usually forget this kind of thing, Boss.
Well…if anyone wants to waste their time believing that, just let them be.
I couldn’t care less.
Thank you.
Hey, it’s already lunch time. Why are you two still working, busy bees?
Hello, Big Boss.
Big Boss! Hello.
Long time no see indeed. I wonder what brought you here today.
Probably to see the lady boss, am I right?
She’s in the office. Let me take you there then.
-This way, please.
- Oh, but…
I’m afraid she already left.
But the last time I checked, she's still in the office.
She has gone out.
Hold on! Stop it.
You two haven’t changed one bit.
One minute, you’re friends. Then you’re at each other’s throat.
Well, today…I’m not here to see Nam.
I’m here to see…
Are you Chonlada?
Er…Yes, I’m Chonlada.
I’m here to see you, Chonlada.
- What?
It’s already lunch time, isn’t it?
How come Nam still keeps you hustling with work.
She’s such a bad boss.
Come and have lunch with me, will you?
I have a lot to talk to you.
Where is Chonlada?
Big Boss, can you eat spicy food?
It seems I ended up ordering only spicy dishes.
Sure.
Come on, let’s dig in.
By the way, you know what?
Since we’re not working right now,
you can stop calling me Big Boss.
Call me ‘Dad’ like Nam does.
Oh, that’s all right.
I think it’d be more appropriate to call you Big Boss like the others.
But you’re Nam’s girlfriend, aren’t you?
I heard you’re seeing each other.
No, that’s not it.
My relationship with Miss Apo is strictly professional—just a boss and an employee.
No need to be afraid. You can be honest with me.
I might be old but I’m quite open when it comes to love.
Whether with a girl or a guy, as long as you love each other;
I’m happy for you both.
So…Nam is a workaholic, isn’t she?
All she does is work and barely has time for you.
Don’t worry, I’ll talk to her about it.
It’s not like that.
I don’t think being workaholic is a bad thing.
On the other hand, I see it more like a dedication in work.
And I actually find it very charming.
Huh? Do you really think that?
Yes, I also love to work.
If the person I am seeing also loves to work like me,
I’ll support her fully.
I can’t believe it. There’s still someone who understands her.
Listen, thank you so much for coming into my daughter’s life.
Dad, why are you taking my staff out here?
Why, of course, to have lunch.
I just want to get to know the person you’re dating.
Chonlada and I are not dating.
No need to hide it from me.
I already approved of you and her seeing each other.
That’s because…
I like you, Lada.
Chonlada. Chonlada!
Get up. Or do you want to stay here?
Please excuse me.
Boss!
Please listen to me first, Boss.
I didn’t ask him to take me out for lunch.
Boss!
Your dad invited me out!
How could I say no to him?
Hey, Boss! Did you hear what…
You’re such a troublemaker.
It’s true that my dad invited you.
But there’s a way to turn down his offer.
You’re making everyone here getting the wrong idea.
You’re blaming me? Don’t you accuse me like that!
Isn’t this all your fault?
What did I do?
If you hadn’t locked me up in that room until morning,
no one would have seen us at all.
Then, go and fix the rumour.
Tell everyone what actually happened.
You’re the boss.
Go tell them yourself. They will definitely listen to you.
But if they don’t hear it from your side too, how can we settle it?
We have to tell them the same side of the story.
Then let them think all they want.
Because after all, it’s not true anyway.
It’s not like I like you, Chonlada.
You’re such a control freak!
What was that?
At first, I was planning to find a way to get us out of this.
But after seeing how you react, I’ve changed my mind.
I couldn’t be bothered.
What a waste of time.
Chonlada.
Yes, Miss Preem?
Miss Lom wants to see you, Boss.
Where is she now?
Ouch, that hurts!
- Let me go!
- Don’t!
If you get out of the car, I’ll fire you.
Why are you taking me here?
Obviously not to kill you and dump your body here.
I’ve wasted enough time with all this nonsense.
Then take me back.
Do you think I drove here…
only to let you boss me around?
I’ll go back myself then.
You can’t go now.
You often say something and mean another, don't you?
Why?
You said you don’t like me, that you don’t want to stay close to me.
But all you do is trying to keep me with you alone.
I wonder if you want to stop the rumour or escalate it even more.
That’s not what I think.
Then, why are you taking me here?
To stop the rumour about us.
Then, try talking to me nicely.
You’re crossing the line, Chonlada.
Is that a no?
Since you have no problem with me,
how about we make the rumour come true then?
If you refuse to talk to me nicely,
then have fun living with the rumour.
Chonlada!
Miss Chonlada!
Can we talk, please?
Oh, so you've agreed to talk to me nicely, Boss?
Please tell me your plan.
Oh dear.
I’m afraid it’s too late, Boss
I already called the cab.
It should arrive in a minute.
Please excuse me then.
Wait!
You can’t leave.
Why?
Or are you afraid I’ll go back to see Miss Wayo at the hotel?
How did you know she’s at the hotel?
Miss Wayo has come looking for me especially.
Don’t you think the staff would be talking?
You’re really…
I never thought you’d be possessive of your sister.
Wait, or are you actually…
possessive of me?
You can believe whatever you want.
But if you don’t tell me your plan,
I’ll take care of it my way.
How?
Whatever the cause of the problem is,
I’ll just get rid of it.
Are you going to fire me, Boss?
That’s fine!
Weren’t you begging for a second chance back then?
I thought you didn’t want to get fired.
But right now I have backups like Big Boss and Miss Wayo.
I’m pretty sure if your dad knows,
he wouldn’t allow you to fire me.
Tell me your plan!
-But…
- Quickly!
So, you’re not going to fire me now?
Just tell me.
If you want me to tell you, try asking me nicely first.
Smile a little.
All right. The only way to stop this rumour is to make it about work.
Impossible.
Why impossible?
You want me to suddenly promote you to be Miss Preem’s assistant.
What would other people think?
Well, they’d think it was all about work that kept us together,
until three in the morning that night.
Like they would believe it.
Probably not at first.
But after I get promoted, they’ll surely believe it.
But we’ve never had that position before.
[Meeting Room 2]
Where are you going, Boss?
To inspect work by the beach.
But you have a meeting in 10 minutes.
I have a meeting today?
Yes, you’ve called for a meeting with the marketing and PR teams…
to discuss about our hotel’s new campaign.
Do you want me to postpone it?
No, leave it be.
Are you all right, Boss?
I can postpone the meeting if you want to get some rest.
I’m fine.
But you’ve never forgotten your schedule before.
If there’s anything I can help, you can always say it.
Miss Preem.
Do you want an assistant?
Sure, Ma’am. Just a moment, please.
Please fill in the information here, sir.
Thank you.
- Nuch.
- Yes?
I can take it from here if you want.
Oh, that’s all right, Lada.
Didn’t you just have lunch?
Why don’t you go sit and relax for a while first?
I can do it.
It’s really nothing, Lada.
But if you do want to help, then…Here.
Can you please handle the guests who might want to check in online? That’s all.
I’ll take care of the rest.
Sure.
How nice.
Messing around to create a rumour…
so that you don’t have to work.
Miss Chonlada.
You can go with Miss Preem.
She just told me you’re no longer working for this department.
You’ll be transferred to another unit.
Excuse me? Transferred?
Where…where will she be transferred to?
Please come with me.
I’ve already set up a desk for you as my assistant.
Assistant?
So, Miss Wadee.
Is Lada now Miss Preem’s assistant?
That’s right. Miss Preem said
Chonalada is quite productive, plus she can speak many languages.
She also has good management skills.
She has been helping Miss Preem lately.
That night when she was seen leaving the meeting room with Boss,
it was because she had to do the work for Miss Preem.
No doubt the rumour isn’t true at all.
Now, has that answered your question?
Yes, crystal clear.
Miss Preem.
When you said you’ve prepared a desk for me, is it around here?
Of course not. It’s upstairs next to my desk, in front of Boss’s office.
Then…why are you taking me here?
Today, you have to go with Boss to meet with her appointments.
What about you? Aren’t you coming with us?
You might be her assistant,
but I’m still the one who evaluates your performance.
She only takes care of the documents.
As for you, follow me to work on-site.
Do I have to tell you everything?
Go drive.
I don’t know how to drive.
What?
You can’t blame me, Boss.
Not all of us were born knowing how to drive.
Besides, it’s not like I don’t want to do it.
But…my family doesn’t encourage us women to do what men do.
My older brothers have their own cars, so they had to learn how to drive.
I don’t have one, so my family told me to use public transportation instead.
Why dramatic all of a sudden?
I didn’t mean to be dramatic. I just wanted to explain it.
While I’m driving, read these documents Miss Preem has prepared for us.
We’ll reach there in half an hour.
Make sure you memorise everything.
All of them?
It’s a lot. How could I memorise them in time?
If you read every single line like that, it’d probably take you all day.
Just memorise the key points.
We’ll set up this side for salad bar, appetizers, and salad dressings.
The main dishes will be here–be it pork, fish, or chicken. Put all of them here.
And this side is a vegetarian zone. Make sure to put up a clear sign and provide different sets of dishes and utensils.
-Chef Ian?
- Next is the dessert zone.
Is she the Michelin-star chef who went on an international cooking show?
It takes years to get an appointment with her, Boss.
It doesn’t matter how famous you are, you still have to wait.
Get yourself together. I know all that.
Do you have an appointment with them?
Oh, okay. That’s all then.
Hello.
Hello, Chef.
Thank you for giving us your valuable time.
My pleasure.
This is Miss Chonlada, my secretary’s assistant.
-Hello.
- Hello.
I’ve already prepared the table for you, Miss Apo.
Shall I take you there now to try my food?
Yes.
Do we get to try your food too, Chef?
You cooked it yourself?
Yes.
I’m sorry.
Let’s go then, shall we?
Yes.
Please go ahead and try it.
Miss Chonlada.
Oh, sorry, Boss.
I’m sorry, Chef.
Please don’t be. The customer’s reaction is the chef’s utmost happiness.
Then, can I have one more bite?
Of course.
I’d rather wait until you and Boss finish talking then.
That’s all right. Please try it.
Thank you.
Actually, I think I know why you’re here, Miss Apo.
I hope you’ll finally agree and give us Watin Group the honour to welcome you this time.
You just don’t know how to give up, do you?
I had turned down your offer for so many times.
I’ll keep asking until you agree to work with us.
I’m beginning to soften up a bit now.
I still insist that no one else is suitable for this project other than you, Chef.
Wow, I really appreciate that.
How about you try it first?
Okay. Thank you.
It’s really good.
What project are you planning to do with Chef Ian, Boss?
Haven’t you read the documents?
But there wasn’t any part that talks about Chef Ian.
Only how to dispose of waste to help save the environment,
which is usually a fundamental knowledge for everyone, isn’t it?
I don’t see any information that’s supposed to be confidential.
Why? Do you want to have access to the hotel’s confidential information?
No, not at all. I was just explaining.
You want me to help Miss Preem, don’t you? If I came to work knowing nothing,
people might find it suspicious and think that I only got promoted because you want to keep me close to you.
And they might start another rumour.
Has anyone ever contacted you to go to Lopburi?
No. Why?
In case you can talk and make those monkeys fall asleep.
Well, you hardly utter a word while I can’t stop talking.
We’re a perfect match, aren’t we?
Anyway, what project are you planning to do with Chef Ian?
Hey, look out!
Are you all right?
I’m okay, Boss. Are you all right?
I’m so sorry. Are you all right, Miss Apo?
There was a call so I got distracted and wasn’t looking.
So, are you sure you and your friend are okay?
Yes.
This is Chonlada, my secretary’s assistant.
Huh? What about Miss Preem?
She’s at the office.
You must be very busy. That's why you have to hire another secretary.
That’s understandable though, because right now the Watin Group’s hotels and resorts…
are indeed second to none.
Please don’t say that.
If there’s nothing else, please excuse us then.
Did you come here to eat at Chef Ian’s restaurant?
I came for that too. But her assistant said she already had an appointment.
I guess that appointment was you then, Miss Apo.
Actually, I’ve arranged an appointment with her beforehand many months ago.
Mine is since last year but she still can’t give me her time slot.
It only took you months to get to meet with her.
Maybe I’ll have to ask for your advice.
Why is it that you’re always one step ahead of the others?
Well actually, you’ve been in this business before me, Mr. Pheempat.
It’s rather me who has to ask for your advice.
Will you excuse us then? We have another matter to attend to.
Sure. It’s a pleasure to meet you here.
And a pleasure to meet you too, Miss Chonlada.
Who removed your plug?
What plug?
A plug to charge a battery for your mouth.
You’ve been quiet since we left the restaurant.
Or are you still in shock because you almost got hit by a car?
Thank you for your concern, Boss.
You didn’t even get hit, is your brain not functioning properly now?
If you’re not worried about me, just deny it. What’s so hard about that?
Hearing that, you seem pretty fine to me.
I feel bad for Miss Preem though.
She’s just lost a chance to get rid of her annoying assistant.
I’m sorry, Boss. Are you all right?
Don’t you have eyes? Can’t you see I already stopped?
Then why didn’t you tell me you’d stop?
How could you blame it on me?
Listen, I just want to tell you that you don’t have to follow me anymore.
I’ll go inspect work by the beach.
You should go tell Miss Preem to prepare documents for the campaign we’ll be promoting during the low season this year.
Yes, Boss.
From next month onwards, we’ll offer mid-year promotions for the rainy season.
The number of tourists, both Thai and foreign, will drop dramatically
And when we have less bookings, it’ll certainly affect the costs, especially our payrolls.
Same amount of staff but less amount of income.
Is that why Boss came up with this campaign to attract more customers…
and increase the booking rate?
Then, can we reduce the room rate?
You can. But that’s what other hotels would do too.
So, the booking rate won’t increase that much.
That’s why Boss wants Chef Ian to work with us on this campaign.
Yes. She’s so talented and extremely hard to get an appointment with.
So, if we can get her to cook for our hotel, that’d help increase our booking rate, right?
At first, when Boss told me that you’d be my assistant;
to be honest, I had so many doubts in my mind.
Boss doesn’t easily trust anyone to work closely with her.
I got this job because my aunt used to be the Big Boss’s secretary.
He certified me for the job.
why did Boss agree to let you work with her so easily?
I think I understand now.
You understand what?
She must have known more about you than I do.
Know what about me?
Boss probably knows what someone who’s confident like you could do to help.
At least, you’re not afraid to be honest with her…
rather than lying just to please her.
You’re also a fast learner as if you had an experience working at a hotel before.
I did an internship while studying.
That’s why I learnt about the hotel system pretty fast.
But there’s still a lot I have to learn, and you must teach me that.
Well then, I’ll go destroy these documents first.
I’ll be right back to help.
Boo!
A scaredy cat as usual.
You scared me to death, Fah!
When did you get here?
Been waiting for you since afternoon.
I took so many naps.
- You scared me.
- I miss you. Give me a hug.
Miss you so much.
Hold on. Stop it. Stop.
- Let me go.
- Miss you so much.
- It’s been a long time.
- Don’t lie.
- We talked on the phone a few days ago.
- Please give me a hug. Pleaseeee.
Fah! Behave.
What do you mean you miss me? We just talked a few days ago.
But it’s not like seeing you in person.
You also don’t have time for me at all.
Mum’s complaining now.
I’ll find some time to Facetime her then.
Why did you come to Thailand?
To get a scoop?
Not really.
I still don’t find any interesting topics.
So, I’ll come live with you in the meantime.
If there happens to be anything interesting, I’ll think about it then.
But I’m not sure if you’ll have time for me though.
I heard you already have a girlfriend.
Did Dad tell you?
I want to see your girlfriend.
Can I go see my future sister-in-law tomorrow?
Can I see her? Pleaseee.
- Can I?
- Chonlada and I are not together.
Wait, Miss Chonlada?
Chonlada means waves.
Apo means water.
What else could this be if not soulmates?
That woman has already given me enough headache.
No need to create more problems for me.
Not to mention Lom.
And that rumour. And Dad too.
Why are you smiling?
Miss Chonlada isn’t the first woman who came into your life.
So?
But you’ve never talked about any woman like this before.
Fah.
I guess she might be that someone who can finally make your icy heart waver.
I’m not talking to you then.
That’s fine. I can go talk to your dad.
Uncle! Uncle!
How was it? Did she mention anything about Lada?
She kept denying but she just couldn’t stop talking about her.
So, do you think she likes her?
I’d say 80% positive, Uncle.
Okay.
Uncle, do you know what Miss Chonlada’s, my future sister-in-law’s family name is?
Why?
I’m just being nosy as usual.
If I ask Nam, she definitely wouldn’t tell me.
I want to use my connection as a journalist to find out about Miss Chonlada more.
Did Apo just let you out?
Pat?
How did you get here?
Why didn’t you tell me…
that you’re now her secretary’s assistant?
I just got promoted today.
Besides, I never thought I’d get to see you and Miss Apo together.
I’m sorry. I only stopped by to see Chef Ian.
But I’m glad that you can get close to Apo this fast.
This way, you can help dig out more information for me.
So, did Chef Ian finally agree to work with the Watin Group?
And what project that your boss is planning to do with her?
[Lada]: I miss you.
But I don’t miss you.
[Lada]: I want to talk to you.
But I don’t want to talk to you.
[Lada]: I have something to tell you about Pat.
I don’t want to hear it!
[Lada]: Not answering means you’re still mad at me.
[Lada]: I’ll go tell it to someone else then. I won’t bother you anymore.
Whatever.
So?
So what?
You’re the one who texted me first.
You forgave me, right?
No, but it’s annoying.
If I hadn’t call you, I guess you would’ve texted me all night.
So, how is it?
Disguising yourself as an employee at your rival’s hotel.
Have you got any insider news for your brothe
Yes.
Miss Apo is trying to get Chef Ian to work with her on a new project.
But I didn’t tell my brother that.
Huh? Why not?
[Pheempat]: What project that your boss is planning to do with Chef Ian?
I really have no idea.
But weren’t you also there at the restaurant with her?
How come you didn’t get any information?
Like I said, this is my first day as her assistant.
She still doesn't trust me that much.
I’m afraid I don’t have anything for you.
Lada…
You do know that you’re my only hope, don’t you?
If my hotel becomes a success, it’s not just me that you could save.
But you could also save the Wachara Group as a whole.
And Dad will look at you with new eyes.
But if my hotel goes down,
apart from me losing all the credits in Dad’s eyes;
you’ll end up being just a daughter who’s merely nothing,
but an object to trade-off for business negotiations.
Do you understand what I mean?
I’ve never forgotten why I chose to work at the Watin Group.
Then, why didn’t you tell your brother about Chef Ian?
Because Miss Apo didn’t play dirty to get Chef Ian to work with her.
But if one day the Watin Group ever tries to play dirty with the Wachara Group,
I’ll tell my brother everything.
I totally agree and I support you fully.
We should at least play it fair and square.
But honestly, maybe it’s better if you back out before Miss Apo would find out who you really are.
Back out?
Do you know how hard it is to get attention from someone who doesn’t care about the world like her,
and make her finally remember my name
I can’t back out right now.
I can only go forward, and make her trust me.
I need to dig out more information from the Watin Group.
You’d better be careful then.
You’ve put yourself inside the lion’s den. It’s risky.
But I’m afraid something is riskier.
Riskier? What do you mean?
Listen to me, Lada. You’re playing with people’s feelings.
You’re in this game too. Just make sure you won’t fall into your own trap.
Wait, you think I’d fall for her?
Dream on.
You can place your bet.
I’ll definitely win.
Nate, I have another call. I’ll call you back.
Huh? What the…
Hello, who’s speaking?
It’s me.
Boss? How did you get my number?
The HR department has all of the staff’s phone numbers.
You’re my secretary’s assistant.
Do you think it’s that hard to get your number?
I’m sorry. I totally forgot my boss has an extremely high IQ.
Calling me at this hour, what can I do for you?
Have you taken your pills?
Yes?
Miss Preem told me you walked back home in the rain.
Take some medicine too.
And don’t think it’s because I’m concerned.
I’m not worried about you.
I’m more worried about myself.
I don’t want to work with a sick person.
It wouldn’t be good if I also catch a cold.
That’s all.
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
[Next Episode]
[Lada]: I just came to check, in case the Watin Group might be cheating.
Aren’t you afraid you’ll get caught?
[Nam]: What are you doing?
I’m taking a look at Chef Ian’s signature dishes…
that she’d make for our campaign opening.
[Pheempat]: Make sure Chef Ian will never want to work with the Watin Group again.
And blame it all on the Watin Group.
[Nam]: Watin Group…
isn’t built by just a person or two.
But by everyone from all departments.
And one of them is you, Chonlada.
[Lada]: I’ll make you admit it one day that I’m good at my job.
[Nam]: Good. I’ll be waiting.
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
♫Honestly, I can’t help but still doubt it♫
♫Are you really that person my heart has been looking for?♫
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
[Waves of Deception]